Gross, James A. Arbitration Files 5697
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- New York State Electric and Gas Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, System Council U-7, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- New York State Electric and Gas Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, System Council U-7, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- New York State Electric and Gas Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, System Council U-7, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- New York State Electric and Gas Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, System Council U-7, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- New York State Electric and Gas Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, System Council U-7, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  Issue: Arbitration Proceedings--Pay For Meetings. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- New York State Electric and Gas Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, System Council U-7, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- New York State Electric and Gas Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, System Council U-7, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- New York State Electric and Gas Corporation vs. System Council U-7 of the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  Issue: Discipline--Demotion As. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- New York State Electric and Gas Corporation vs. System Council U-7 of the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- New York State Electric and Gas Corporation vs. System Council U-7 of the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- New York State Electric and Gas Corporation vs. System Council U-7 of the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- New York State Electric and Gas Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, System Council U-7, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Assignment To Work Outside Of Classification. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- New York State Electric and Gas Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, System Council U-7, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- New York State Electric and Gas Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, System Council U-7, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- New York State Electric and Gas Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, System Council U-7, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- New York State Electric and Gas Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, System Council U-7, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- New York State Nurses' Association vs. The House of the Good Samaritan, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  Issue: Holidays and Holiday Pay--Computation. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- New York State Nurses' Association vs. The House of the Good Samaritan, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- New York State Nurses' Association vs. The House of the Good Samaritan, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- New York Telephone vs. Communications Workers of America (Box 13, Folder 25)
  NA, AN, RC.
- New York Telephone Company vs. Telephone Traffic Union, Upstate New York, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  Issue: Holidays and Holiday Pay--Holiday As Mandatory Workday. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- New York Telephone Company vs. Telephone Traffic Union, Upstate New York, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- New York Telephone Company vs. Telephone Traffic Union, Upstate New York, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- New York Telephone Company vs. Telephone Traffic Union, Upstate New York, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Niagara Frontier Services, Incorporated vs. Retail Clerks Union, Local No. 212, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Niagara Frontier Services, Incorporated vs. Retail Clerks Union, Local No. 212, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Niagara Frontier Transportation Authority vs. International Longshoremen's Association, Local No. 2028, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  Issue: Rates of Pay--Wage Hold Back. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Niagara Frontier Transportation Authority vs. International Longshoremen's Association, Local No. 2028, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Niagara Frontier Transportation Authority vs. International Longshoremen's Association, Local No. 2028, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- Niagara Frontier Transit Metro System, Incorporated vs. Amalgamated Transit Union, Local Union No. 1342, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  Issue: Schedules of Work-- Holiday and Time Off Schedules. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Niagara Frontier Transit Metro System, Incorporated vs. Amalgamated Transit Union, Local Union No. 1342, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- Niagara Frontier Transit Metro System, Incorporated vs. Amalgamated Transit Union, Local Union No. 1342, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- North Syracuse Central School District vs. North Syracuse Education Association, Local No. 2881, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  Issue: Contract Interpretation--Job Description. EX, AN, RC, A.
- North Syracuse Central School District vs. North Syracuse Education Association, Local No. 2881, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- North Syracuse Central School District vs. North Syracuse Education Association, Local No. 2881, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Onondaga Central School District vs. Onondaga Central Non-Instructional Association, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Procedure. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Onondaga Central School District vs. Onondaga Central Non-Instructional Association, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Onondaga Central School District vs. Onondaga Central Non-Instructional Association, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Onondaga Central School District vs. Onondaga Central Non-Instructional Association, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Onondaga Central School District vs. Onondaga Central Non-Instructional Association, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Onondaga Central School District vs. Onondaga Central Non-Instructional Association, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Onondaga Central School District vs. Onondaga Central Non-Instructional Association, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Onondaga, the County of vs. Civil Service Employees Association, Incorporated, Onondaga Local No. 834, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  Issue: Absences--Excessive. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Onondaga, the County of vs. Civil Service Employees Association, Incorporated, Onondaga Local No. 834, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Onondaga, the County of vs. Civil Service Employees Association, Incorporated, Onondaga Local No. 834, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Onondaga County Water Authority vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 317, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  Issue: Vacations--Computation. EX, AN, RC, A.
- Onondaga County Water Authority vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 317, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Onondaga County Water Authority vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 317, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  Issue: Vacations--Eligibility. EX, AN, RC, A.
- Onondaga County Water Authority vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 317, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Onondaga County Water Authority vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 317, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Potsdam Paper Corporation vs. United Paperworkers International Union, Local No. 1726, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  Issue: Discipline--Discharge; Improper Personal Conduct--Defacing or Destroying Property. EX, AN, RC, A.
- Potsdam Paper Corporation vs. United Paperworkers International Union, Local No. 1726, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Redmond Plastics, Incorporated vs. Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union of America, AFL-CIO-CLC, Local No. 1827, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  Issue: Absences--Discipline; Tardiness--Discipline. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Redmond Plastics, Incorporated vs. Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union of America, AFL-CIO-CLC, Local No. 1827, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Redmond Plastics, Incorporated vs. Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union of America, AFL-CIO-CLC, Local No. 1827, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Rensselaer County vs. Civil Service Employees Association, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Local 1000, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  Issue: Arbitrability--Schedules of Work. EX, AN, RC, A.
- Rensselaer County vs. Civil Service Employees Association, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Local 1000, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Rochester Telephone Corporation vs. Communications Workers of America, Local No. 1170, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Temporary Assignment. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Rochester Telephone Corporation vs. Communications Workers of America, Local No. 1170, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Rochester Telephone Corporation vs. Communications Workers of America, Local No. 1170, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Rochester Telephone Corporation vs. Communications Workers of America, Local No. 1170 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Schlegel Corporation vs. Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, Local No. 3T, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  Issue: Contracting Out--Bargaining Unit Work. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Schlegel Corporation vs. Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, Local No. 3T, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Schlegel Corporation vs. Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, Local No. 3T, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Schlegel Corporation vs. Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, Local No. 3T, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Schlegel Corporation vs. Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, Local No. 3T, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  Issue: Arbitrability; Physical Disability-- Termination of Employment Following. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Schlegel Corporation vs. Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, Local No. 3T, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Schlegel Corporation vs. Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, Local No. 3T, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Schuyler-Chemung-Tioga BOCES vs. Schuyler-Chemung-Tioga BOCES Educational Support Staff Association, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs-- Added Duties. TR, EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Schuyler-Chemung-Tioga BOCES vs. Schuyler-Chemung-Tioga BOCES Educational Support Staff Association, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 38)
- Schuyler-Chemung-Tioga BOCES vs. Schuyler-Chemung-Tioga BOCES Educational Support Staff Association, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 39)
- Schuyler-Chemung-Tioga BOCES vs. Schuyler-Chemung-Tioga BOCES Educational Support Staff Association, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 40)
- Shepard Niles Crane and Hoist Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local Lodge 1765, District 58, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  Issue: Discipline--Discharge. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Shepard Niles Crane and Hoist Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local Lodge 1765, District 58, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 42)
- Social Security Administration Office of Hearings and Appeals vs. American Federation of Government Employees, Local No. 1760 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  Issue: Promotions--Eligibility. NA, EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Social Security Administration Office of Hearings and Appeals vs. American Federation of Government Employees, Local No. 1760 (Box 14, Folder 44)
- Social Security Administration Office of Hearings and Appeals vs. American Federation of Government Employees, Local No. 1760 (Box 14, Folder 45)
- Social Security Administration Office of Hearings and Appeals vs. American Federation of Government Employees, Local No. 1760 (Box 14, Folder 46)
- St. Joseph's Hospital vs. New York State Nurses Association, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Shift Scheduling. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- St. Joseph's Hospital vs. New York State Nurses Association, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- St. Joseph's Hospital vs. New York State Nurses Association, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Sterling Winthrop Research Institute, Division of Sterling Drug, Incorporated vs. International Chemical Workers Union, Local 61 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  NA, EX, AN, RC, A.
- Sterling Winthrop Research Institute, Division of Sterling Drug, Incorporated vs. International Chemical Workers Union, Local 61 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Sterling Organics, Division of Sterling Drug, Incorporated vs. International Chemical Workers Union, Local 61, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs-- Ability vs. Seniority. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Sterling Organics, Division of Sterling Drug, Incorporated vs. International Chemical Workers Union, Local 61, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Sterling Organics (U.S.), Division of Sterling Drug, Incorporated vs. International Chemical Workers Union, Local 61, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  Issue: Contracting Out-- Bargaining Unit Work. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Sterling Organics (U.S.), Division of Sterling Drug, Incorporated vs. International Chemical Workers Union, Local 61, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Syracuse, City of vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Council 66, Local Union 400, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  Issue: Discipline--Discharge; Improper Personal Conduct--Drinking; Leaving Plant or Work Area Without Permission. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Syracuse, City of vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Council 66, Local Union 400, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Syracuse, City of vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Council 66, Local Union 400, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Syracuse, City of vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Council 66, Local Union 400, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Syracuse, City of vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Council 66, Local Union 400, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Syracuse, City of vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), Incorporated, Onondaga Chapter, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  Issue: Arbitrability--Promotions. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Syracuse, City of vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), Incorporated, Onondaga Chapter, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Syracuse, City of vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), Incorporated, Onondaga Chapter, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Syracuse, City of vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), Incorporated, Onondaga Chapter, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Syracuse, City of vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), Incorporated, Onondaga Chapter, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Syracuse, City of vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), Incorporated, Onondaga Local 834, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  Issue: Discipline--Discharge; Improper Job Attitude--Insubordination. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Syracuse, City of vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), Incorporated, Onondaga Local 834, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Syracuse, City of vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), Incorporated, Onondaga Local 834, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Syracuse, City of vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), Incorporated, Onondaga Local 834, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Syracuse, City of vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), Incorporated, Onondaga Local 834, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Syracuse, City of vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), Incorporated, Onondaga Local 834, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Syracuse, City of vs. Officers Cossellman and Sears, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  Issue: Discipline--Basis. AN, RC
- Syracuse, City of vs. Officers Cossellman and Sears, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Syracuse, City of vs. Syracuse Fire Fighters' Association, Local 280, International Association of Firefighters, AFL-CIO (Box 15, Folder 28)
  NA, AN, RC, A.
- Syracuse, City of vs. Syracuse Fire Fighters' Association, Local 280, International Association of Firefighters, AFL-CIO (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Syracuse, City of vs. Syracuse Police Benevolent Association, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  Issue: Discipline--Basis. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Syracuse, City of vs. Syracuse Police Benevolent Association, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- Syracuse, City of vs. Syracuse Police Benevolent Association, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Syracuse, City of vs. Syracuse Police Benevolent Association, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Syracuse, City of vs. Syracuse Police Benevolent Association, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Syracuse, City of vs. Syracuse Police Benevolent Association (PBA) (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Syracuse University vs. Service Employees International Union (SEIU), Local 200, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Ability vs. Seniority. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Syracuse University vs. Service Employees International Union (SEIU), Local 200, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Syracuse University vs. Service Employees International Union (SEIU), Local 200, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Syracuse University vs. General Service Employees' International Union, Local 200, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  Issue: Discipline--Discharge; Alcoholism, Drinking, and Intoxication--Drinking on the Job. TR, EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Syracuse University vs. General Service Employees' International Union, Local 200, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Syracuse University vs. General Service Employees' International Union, Local 200, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Syracuse University vs. General Service Employees' International Union, Local 200, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Tonawanda, Town of vs. Town of Tonawanda Salaried Workers Association, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  Issue: Fringe Benefits--Insurance and Medical Plans. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Tonawanda, Town of vs. Town of Tonawanda Salaried Workers Association, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Tonawanda, Town of vs. Town of Tonawanda Salaried Workers Association, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Tonawanda, Town of vs. Town of Tonawanda Salaried Workers Association, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Tully Central School District vs. Robert F. Thompson, Respondent Tenured Teacher (Box 16, Folder 9)
  Issue: Incompetence and Inefficiency--Discipline (Section 3020-A Education Law Proceeding). AN, RC.
- Tully Central School District vs. Robert F. Thompson, Respondent Tenured Teacher (Box 16, Folder 10)
- U.S. Customs Service vs. National Treasury Employees Union (Box 16, Folder 11)
  NA, RC, SD.
- U.S. Customs Service vs. National Treasury Employees Union (Box 16, Folder 12)
- U.S. Customs Service vs. National Treasury Employees Union (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Universal Foods Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Local Union No. 687-Plant, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  Issue: Promotions--Seniority. EX, AN, RC, A.
- Universal Foods Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Local Union No. 687-Plant, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Utica City School District vs. Utica Teachers Association, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Added Duties. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Utica City School District vs. Utica Teachers Association, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Utica City School District vs. Utica Teachers Association, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Utica City School District vs. Utica Teachers Association, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- WTVH, Meredith Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Local Union No. 317, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  Issue: Termination of Employment--Discrimination. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- WTVH, Meredith Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Local Union No. 317, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- WTVH, Meredith Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Local Union No. 317, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- WTVH, Meredith Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Local Union No. 317, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Waterloo Central School District vs. Waterloo Education Association, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Waterloo Central School District vs. Waterloo Education Association, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Waterloo Central School District vs. Waterloo Education Association, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Waterloo Central School District vs. Waterloo Education Association, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Waterloo Central School District vs. Waterloo Education Association, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Waterloo Central School District vs. Waterloo Education Association, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Watervliet Arsenal vs. National Association of Government Employees, Local R2-98, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  Issue: Testing of Employees--Training and Trial Periods. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Watervliet Arsenal vs. National Association of Government Employees, Local R2-98, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Watervliet Arsenal vs. National Association of Government Employees, Local R2-98, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Watervliet Arsenal vs. National Association of Government Employees, Local R2-98, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Watervliet Arsenal vs. National Association of Government Employees, Local R2-98, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- Watervliet Arsenal vs. National Association of Government Employees, Local R2-98, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- West Canada Valley School vs. West Canada Valley School Unit, Civil Service Employees Association, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  Issue: Recall-Seniority. AN, RC.
- Westmoreland Central School District vs. Westmoreland Non-Instructional Employees Service Organization, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  Issue: Vacations--Unauthorized. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Westmoreland Central School District vs. Westmoreland Non-Instructional Employees Service Organization, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 38)
- Westmoreland Central School District vs. Westmoreland Non-Instructional Employees Service Organization, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 39)
- Williamsville Central School District vs. Williamsville Teachers Association, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 40)
- Williamsville Central School District vs. Williamsville Teachers Association, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 41)
- Williamsville Central School District vs. Williamsville Teachers Association, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 42)
- Wyoming Correctional Facility vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Council 82 (Box 16, Folder 43)